Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XLV. GRAND LODGE OFFICERS
  - Sub-Series 297-32. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Rapoport, W.- Rypstat, E.W., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 14)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. St. John, A.R., Jr.- Strahorn, M.C., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 15)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Tait, W.A.- Youngberg, W.B., 1936-1949 (Box 480, Folder 16)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1941-1947 (Box 481, Folder 1)
      1941-August 1947.
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1936-1949 (Box 481, Folder 2)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1933-1935 (Box 481, Folder 3)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Sylvester, J.H., Vice Grand President., 1933-1934 (Box 481, Folder 4)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. Eastty, G.W. Territory, 1933-1936 (Box 481, Folder 5)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1928 (Box 481, Folder 6)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1926 (Box 481, Folder 7)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1925 (Box 481, Folder 8)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1924 (Box 481, Folder 9)
    - Employment. Grand Lodge Organizers. General, 1923 (Box 481, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 297-33. Grand Lodge Officers
    - Sick Leave. Davie, A.R., 1966 (Box 481, Folder 11)
    - Sick Leave. Clark, J.O., 1963-1966 (Box 481, Folder 12)
    - Sick Leave. Erickson, L.M., 1958-1966 (Box 481, Folder 13)
    - Sick Leave. Gibson, G.W., 1961-1963 (Box 481, Folder 14)
    - Sick Leave. Hartley, J.W., 1963 (Box 481, Folder 15)
    - Sick Leave. Kelly, E.F., 1958-1961 (Box 481, Folder 16)
    - Sick Leave. Lanza, E.A., 1959-1962 (Box 481, Folder 17)
    - Sick Leave. Mose, A., 1960-1962 (Box 481, Folder 18)
    - Sick Leave. McKinney, L., 1959-1961 (Box 481, Folder 19)
    - Sick Leave. Williams, G., 1961-1962 (Box 481, Folder 20)